Su Yurou
Before telling a story
you should at least make sure
whose name is in it
Please tell the truth
Miss Su, please show the originals
The originals
I didn't bring them today
Why not
I was afraid of losing them
so I only brought the copies
You said you've kept
these things all along
Yes
Where did you keep them
What color was the box
Was it wrapped in anything
Was the original receipt folded
What was the pendant placed under
That was 15 years ago
It's normal I can't remember clearly
It is normal
Then how can you be sure
you were the one who saved him
Sister, from the very beginning
did you just not want me to speak
I didn't stop you from speaking
I just asked you to provide full evidence
Su Yurou, you have two choices now
First, show the originals and let Fu Group
and the hospital verify them. Second
admit that you can't prove right now
these things belong to the Fu family
Tears won't validate the past
I just wanted to help Mr. Fu find his past